ILR School Press Releases /3059
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Press Releases
1948-1959
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3059
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Press releases.
Publicity and articles regarding the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8436155
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436155
- Press Releases July 1948 to Nov. 22, 19478 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Press Releases Dec. 13, 1948 to Dec. 27, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Press Releases Jan. 1949 to May, 14, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Press Releases June 3, 1949 to June 21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Press Releases July 7, 1949 to Aug. 10, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Press Releases Sept. 14, 1949 to Feb. 4, 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Press Releases Jan 4, 1949 to Feb. 28, 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Press Releases March 1, 1950 to April 29, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Press Releases May 1, 1950 to June 30, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Press Releases July 6, 1950 to Dec. 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Press Releases Sept. 20, 1951 - Nov. 1, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Press Releases Jan. 1, 1951 - June 30, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Press Releases July 2, 1951 - Sept. 26, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Press Releases Nov. 9, 1951 - Sept. 30, 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Press Releases April 2, 1953 to Sept. 25, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Press Releases Oct. 1, 1952 to March 19, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Press Releases May 3, 1954 to Sept. 20, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Press Releases Oct. 1, 1953 to April 28, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Feature Articles July 1, 1948 to June 30, 1949, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Feature Articles July 1, 1948 to June 30, 1949, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- News Releases Oct, 1 1955 to Sept. 30, 1956, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- News Releases Oct. 1955 - Oct. 1959, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- News Releases Oct. 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- News Releases 10/1/56-9/3/57, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Releases 10/1/54 to 9/30/55, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Releases 10/1/54 to 9/30/55, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)